A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- Store Building, W. Washington St., Norfolk, Va., for Suffolk Star Corp. - Permit Number: None, Address: [1510 Brambleton Ave.], 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1940-12 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  Drawn by: William G. Bursnall, Architect, 404 W. 22nd St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: Suffolk Star Corp.
- Cleaning Plant for H. E. McCoy - Permit Number: None, Address: Brambleton and Clay Aves., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-24 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  Drawn by: V. T. Myers, Contractor, 711 Bankers Trust Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: V. T. Myers; Commissioned by: H. E. McCoy
- [Alterations to 256 and 258 Brewer St. for Rosa Dalton Estate] - Permit Number: None, Address: 256-258 Brewer St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-29 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  Drawn by: A. J. Dalton; Contractor: J. M. Whitman; Commissioned by: Rosa Dalton Estate
- A Store Building for Saint Paul's Episcopal Church - Permit Number: 43749, Address: 235-239 Church St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-26 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  Drawn by: Alan McCullough, Architect; Contractor: W. T. Gregory; Commissioned by: St. Paul's Episcopal Church
- [1 Story Store Building] - Permit Number: 41828, Address: 115 1st View St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-30 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. C. Liverman; Commissioned by: M. Sakakini
- Building at Llewellyn Ave. and 21st St. - Permit Number: 43526, Address: Llewellyn Ave. and 21st. St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-23 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  Drawn by: David Fitz-Gibbon, Architect; Contractor: J. T. Nichols; Commissioned by: Roy V. Ward
- Cinderblock and Stucco Store Building for Madison Cleaners and Tailors - Permit Number: None, Address: S/E Corner of Hampton Blvd. and 39th St., 1940, Media: Blueprints, paper and graphite; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-32 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  Drawn by: C. W. Kassell; Commissioned by: G. R. McBride
- Alterations of Store Building at 438 Boush St. - Permit Number: None, Address: 438 Boush St., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-14 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects; Commissioned by: John Upton, Jr.; John Upton, Sr.- Guardian
- Proposed Alterations to the Store of Mr. Harry Kyrus - Permit Number: 43590, Address: 99th St. and Hampton Blvd., 1940, Media: Blueprints, bumwad, graphite; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-13 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  Drawn by: J. T. Ewell, General Contractor; Contractor: J. T. Ewell; Commissioned by: Harry Kyrus
- Store- [A & P Co.] - Permit Number: None, Address: 1825 E. Brambleton Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 21; Tag Number: 1940-10 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  Drawn by: E. C. Seiz, Architect, Atlanta, Ga.; Contractor: Benjamin J. Massell, Jr.; Notes: Contains drawings for A & P Stores in Newport News and Hampton, Va.
- B. and H. Rosenbaum, Frame Store - Permit Number: 42306, Address: 508 First View St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-46 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  Drawn by: H. Rosenbaum; Contractor: G. A. Peterman; Commissioned by: B. and H. Rosenbaum
- Store to be Renovated for Dr. B. Salasky - Permit Number: 43376, Address: 2204 Hampton Blvd., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-38 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 518 Dickson Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: T. W. Aldridge; Commissioned by: Dr. B. Salasky
- Plan of Suburban Park - Permit Number: None, Address: Yorktown Dr., Granby St., and Suburban Parkway, 1941, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: None (Box 13, Folder 151)
  Drawn by: Hal A. Miller and Associates, Registered Architects; Harry J. Goodwin, Consulting Engineer, 421 St. Paul Place, Baltimore, Md.; Commissioned by: Housing Engineering Corp.
- Baseball Grandstand for Norfolk, Virginia - Permit Number: 42445, Address: Corner of Church and Rugby Sts., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-43 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect, Norfolk; Contractor: Dependable Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Outdoor Athletics, Incorporated
- 911 Graydon Avenue Apartments - Permit Number: None, Address: 911 Graydon Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-18 (Box 13, Folder 153)
  Drawn by: C. A. Neff, Architect; Commissioned by: 911 Graydon Avenue Corp.
- Brick Storage Building - Permit Number: 42612, Address: Foot of Claiborne Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints, bumwad; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-81 (Box 13, Folder 154)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect, Norfolk; Contractor: Dependable Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co.
- Brick Building for Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corp. - Permit Number: 45912, Address: Rose Ave., 1941, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: None (Box 13, Folder 155)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect, Norfolk; Contractor: Dependable Construction; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corp.
- Extension to Machine Shop Crane - Permit Number: 43619, Address: None, 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: None (Box 13, Folder 156)
  Drawn by: Standard Iron and Steel Co., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corp.
- Two Story Brick Warehouse - Permit Number: 47687, Address: Rosa Ave., 1942, Media: Blueprints, paper, graphite; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 13, Folder 157)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect, 716 Boush St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Dependable Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corp.
- [Store Building] - Permit Number: 43448, Address: 115 S. Mowbray Arch, 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-36 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  Drawn by: Bush Construction Company, Inc.; Contractor: Bush Construction Company, Inc.; Commissioned by: W. L. Shepherd
- Four Family Frame and Shingle Apartment to be Built for C. W. Beard and Son - Permit Number: 42124, Address: Gates Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints, paper, graphite; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-53 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  Drawn by: C. W. Beard and Son, General Contractors; Contractor: C. W. Beard and Son; Commissioned by: C. W. Beard and Son
- [Drive-in Restaurant] - Permit Number: 42298, Address: W. Side Granby St. at Bridge, 1940, Media: Blueprints, paper, graphite; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-2 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: R. L. Merrill and C. R. Gunter
- Garage for Southern Materials Corp. - Permit Number: None, Address: 8901 Hampton Blvd., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-39 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Southern Materials Corp.
- Store and Office Building for The Phoenix Corp. - Permit Number: 21863, Address: Ocean View Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-15 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects; Commissioned by: The Phoenix Corp.
- Alterations to Capps Shoe Store - Permit Number: None, Address: S/W Corner of Church and Charlotte Sts., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-4 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: T. W. Aldridge; Commissioned by: ? Shannon
- Garage Building for Beasley and Blanford - Permit Number: None, Address: 2208-2218 Colonial Ave., 1919, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-20 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  Drawn by: B. F. Mitchell, Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Beasley and Blanford; Notes: Includes drawings for alterations to 2208 Colonial Ave.- Permit # 42491- by Globe Iron Construction for Penn Mutual Life Insurance Co. dated 6/4/1940 (3 sheets).
- Four Family Apartment Building for Mr. E. T. Gresham - Permit Number: None, Address: Corner of 26th and Hubbard Sts., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1940-22 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects; Commissioned by: E. T. Gresham
- Two Story Frame Building - Permit Number: None, Address: Lucille Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints, bumwad, graphite; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1940-134 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Mr. and Mrs. J. B. Tillett
- Seay Brothers Apartment at Ocean View - Permit Number: 41794, Address: First View St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-17 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Seay Brothers
- Seay Brothers Apartment at Ocean View - Permit Number: 40616, Address: Maple and Ocean View Aves., 1939, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: None (Box 13, Folder 168)
  Drawn by: Seay Brothers; Contractor: Seay Brothers; Commissioned by: Seay Brothers
- Proposed Alterations at No. 207 and No. 209 City Hall Ave., Norfolk, Va., for National White Tower Systems, Inc. - Permit Number: None, Address: 207-209 City Hall Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-11 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  Drawn by: Construction Dept., White Tower System, 418 W. 42nd St., New York, Ny; Commissioned by: National White Tower Systems, Inc.
- Building at 734-736 E. Main St., Norfolk, Va. - Permit Number: 41765, Address: 734-736 E. Main St., 1940, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-40 (Box 14, Folder 170)
  Drawn by: T. David Fitz-Gibbon, Architect; Contractor: J. T. Nichols; Notes: Building inspection sheet included with plan notes that the original buildings on the site were razed (Permits 41162-63).
- Warehouse Between Warehouses A and B, Sewells Point, Va. - Permit Number: 43722, Address: Sewells Point Rd., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1940-7 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  Drawn by: Norfolk and Western Railway Co., Norfolk Terminal Division, Office of Chief Engineer, Roanoke, Va.; Commissioned by: Norfolk and Western Railway Co.
- Two Story Frame Apartment - Permit Number: 42627, Address: A View Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-19 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  Drawn by: J. W. Korbach; Contractor: J. W. Korbach; Commissioned by: Irene V. Korbach
- Building for Maple Lane Bowling Alley Corp. - Permit Number: None, Address: 21st St. and Colley Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1940-52 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  Drawn by: H. P. Franklin, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: E. E. Weddle and Co.; Commissioned by: Maple Lane Bowling Alley Corp.; Notes: Includes an additional set for the rebuilding of Maple Lane Bowling Alley (partially destroyed by fire) by Bernard B. Spigel, Architect, dated 11/11/1944 (7 sheets and specs.).
- [Four Family Apartment at Ocean View] - Permit Number: 41785, Address: Balview Ave., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-61 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  Drawn by: R. T. Fisk; Commissioned by: Dr. and Mrs. J. L. Deitrick
- Renovation of Store - Permit Number: 43090, Address: 604 Main St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-35 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 518 Dickson Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: A. M. Johnson; Commissioned by: Dr. Cooper
- Addition to Maternity Wing, Norfolk General Hospital - Permit Number: 43731, Address: Raleigh Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1940-6 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  Drawn by: Vernon A. Moore, Architect, 505 Flatiron Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Logan McCloud; Commissioned by: Norfolk General Hospital
- Plans for an Office Building - Permit Number: None, Address: Plume St., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-70 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, Architect
- Twelve Family Masonry Apartment - Permit Number: 42528, Address: N/W Corner of Hampton Blvd. and Dinwiddie St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1940-45 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  Drawn by: Thurmer Hoggard, Jr., 308-309 McKevitt Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: The Baydush Corp.; Commissioned by: B. Baydush
- Alterations and Addition to 755 Church Street, Norfolk, Va., for Mr. D. Levitin and Son - Permit Number: 41335, Address: 755 Church St., 1939, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1940-37 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  Drawn by: Philip B. Moser, Architect and Engineer, 412 Bankers Trust Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: W. E. Williams; Commissioned by: Levitin and Son
- Plans for Converting Residence, S/W Corner Bute and Botetourt Streets for a Nine Unit Efficiency Apartment - Permit Number: 41762, Address: Bute and Botetourt Sts., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-27 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: C. Q. Nugent, General Contractor; Commissioned by: P. H. Rose
- Rebuilding Premises of Saunders Provision Co. - Permit Number: 43215, Address: 271-273 Bank St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1940-54 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  Drawn by: B. F. Mitchell, Architect, Flatiron Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: I. B. Williamson; Commissioned by: Saunders Provision Co.
- Merrimack Park, U. S. H. A. Aided Defense Housing Project VA 6-1 for Housing Authority of the City of Norfolk - Permit Number: None, Address: None, 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 35; Tag Number: 1940-41 (Box 14, Folder 182)
  Drawn by: Norfolk Association of Architects- Vernon A. Moore, Chief Architect, C. A. Neff, T. David Fitz Gibbon, Rudolph Cooke and Van Leeuwen, Bernard B. Spigel and Associate; Commissioned by: Housing Authority of the City of Norfolk
- Housing Project for the Suburban Apartments Corp., Owners, Norfolk, Va. - Permit Number: None, Address: Granby St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 32; Tag Number: 1940-57 (Box 15, Folder 183)
  Drawn by: Hal A. Miller and Associates, Architects; Harry J. Goodwin, Consulting Engineer, Baltimore, Md.; S. W. Armistead, Civil Engineer, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Engineering Construction Corp.; Commissioned by: Suburban Apartments Corp.
- Merrimack Park, U. S. H. A. Aided Defense Housing Project VA 6-1 for Housing Authority of the City of Norfolk - Permit Number: None, Address: None, 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 40; Tag Number: 1940-5 (Box 15, Folder 184)
  Drawn by: Norfolk Association of Architects- Vernon A. Moore, Chief Architect, C. A. Neff, T. David Fitz Gibbon, Rudolph Cooke and Van Leeuwen, Bernard B. Spigel and Associate; Contractor: Ralph Herzog; Commissioned by: Housing Authority of the City of Norfolk; Notes: Set contains a copy of a contract b/t Housing Authority of the City of Norfolk and the City of Norfolk, 9/3/1940.
- Standard 43'-2" x 24'-4" Texaco Type E (with heater room) Two Bay Brick Service Station - Permit Number: 43522, Address: S/S #11 Granby St. and Sewell's Point Rd., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 13; Tag Number: 1940-91 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  Drawn by: The Texas Company, 135 E. 42nd St., New York; Commissioned by: The Texas Co.
- Fire Escape for Southern Produce Building - Permit Number: None, Address: Water St., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-55 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Henkas Realty Corp.
- Gem Theater - Permit Number: 41823, Address: N/W Corner of E. Olney Rd. and Church St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-8 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 518 Dickson Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Notes: Exterior of roll notes "Was Star" [Theater].
- [Service Station] - Permit Number: 42801, Address: Granby, Church, and 32nd St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-84 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  Drawn by: Standard Oil Company of New Jersey, Sales Dept., Construction and Maintenance Div., 26 Broadway, New York.; Commissioned by: Standard Oil Co. of New Jersey
- Plan for Three Stores - Permit Number: 40998, Address: 7519-7523 Granby St., 1939, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1940-25 (Box 15, Folder 189)
  Drawn by: John W. Saunders, Sr., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: John W. Saunders and Son; Commissioned by: Academy Store Corp.; Banks-Hocum
- Five Stores for Banks and Harcum - Permit Number: None, Address: Granby St. and Maycox Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: None (Box 15, Folder 190)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 518 Dickson Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Banks and Harcum; Notes: Outside of roll notes "Academy Stores."
- [Various Alterations to 7501, 7511, 7515, 7523 Granby St.] - Permit Number: None, Address: Granby St., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: None (Box 15, Folder 191)
  Drawn by: Various; Commissioned by: Academy Stores; Notes: This roll consisted of several one six one sheet drawings for various alterations to 7501, 7511, 7515, and 7523 Granby St. by various architects.
- [Store Building] - Permit Number: None, Address: 220 Bute St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1940-16 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  Drawn by:; Contractor: C. Q. Nugent, General Contractor; Commissioned by: Miss S. R. B. Timberlake
- Lumber Warehouse - Permit Number: 31700, Address: S/S 23rd St., 1932, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-86 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: White Lumber Co.
- Alteration Plan - Permit Number: 41757, Address: Corner of Monticello and City Hall Aves., 1939, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-34 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  Drawn by: Robert A. Fash, Architect, 330 W. 42nd St., N.Y.C.; Commissioned by: United Cigar-Whelan Stores Corp.
- Stable - Permit Number: 29259, Address: 2310 Princess Anne Rd., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-59 (Box 15, Folder 195)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: R. R. Richardson and Co.; Commissioned by: The Holly Holding Corp.- E. T. Scott, Sec.
- Alterations of Fire Escape, Eureka Lodge Modern Elks - Permit Number: None, Address: 626 Church St., 1940, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-66 (Box 15, Folder 196)
  Drawn by: Barnum Bruns Iron Works; Commissioned by: Eureka Lodge Modern Elks
- Store Building for Mrs. J. J. Lenney - Permit Number: 15492, Address: Queen St., 1923, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 61; Tag Number: 1940-1 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  Drawn by: A. O. Ferebee, Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: L. McCloud; Commissioned by: Mrs. J. J. Lenney
- Design of Building for I.O.O.F., Norfolk, VA - Permit Number: None, Address: 151-153 Church St., 1911, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-68 (Box 16, Folder 198)
  Drawn by: James W. Lee; Contractor: John H. Pierce; Commissioned by: Independent Order of Odd Fellows; Notes: This is the first I.O.O.F. hall in Norfolk. It was later converted into a department store. Includes a set of drawings for Alterations and Additions to the L. Snyder Department Store, June 1940 (Permit # 42987), by Bernard B. Spigel (4 sheets).
- Stores for 28th and Colley Corp. - Permit Number: 43511, Address: Colley Ave. b/t 27th and 28th Sts., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-31 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  Drawn by: V. T. Myers, Contractor; Contractor: V. T. Myers; Commissioned by: 28th and Colley Corp.
- Building for Yellow Cab Company - Permit Number: None, Address: 740 National Ln., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-44 (Box 16, Folder 200)
  Drawn by: David Fitz-Gibbon, Architect; Commissioned by: Yellow Cab Co.
- [Warehouses for B. and D. L. Margolius] - Permit Number: None, Address: 19th and 20th Sts., 1918, Media: Blueprints, Kraft paper, blueline print; Sheets: 16; Tag Number: None (Box 12, Folder 201)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: B. and D. L. Margolius; Notes: Includes additional sets of plans for adjacent warehouses. Warehouse drawings by Peebles and Ferguson, December 1923 (5 sheets).
- Store for Mr. Harry Comess - Permit Number: None, Address: 152-154 Church St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 23; Tag Number: 1940-126 (Box 16, Folder 202)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 518 Dickson Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Harry Comess
- Plan for Open Garage on Premises - Permit Number: 43382, Address: 946-954 Park Ave., 1940, Media: Heavy paper; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-112 (Box 16, Folder 203)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: T. W. Jones
- Warehouse and Offices of Norfolk Sash and Door Co. - Permit Number: 33786, Address: 1320 Boissevain Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-111 (Box 16, Folder 204)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Norfolk Sash and Door Co.
- Steel Works, Alterations to 153 Bank St. - Permit Number: None, Address: 153 Bank St., 1924, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-123 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  Drawn by: W. T. Gregory; Contractor: W. T. Gregory
- Store and Apartment Building - Permit Number: None, Address: 21st and Omohundro Sts., ca. 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-95 (Box 16, Folder 206)
  Drawn by: E. Tucker Carlton, Architect, Richmond, Va.
- Monticello Avenue Store Building - Permit Number: 42779, Address: E. side Monticello Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints, Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-103 (Box 16, Folder 207)
  Drawn by: E. C. Seiz, Architect; Commissioned by: Ben J. Massell, Jr.
- Plot Plan and Addition to Warehouses for the Holly Corp. - Permit Number: 31251, Address: 2300 Princess Anne Rd., 1932, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-100 (Box 16, Folder 208)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Holly Corp.
- Proposed Office Building - Permit Number: 43257, Address: Mulberry St., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1940-121 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  Drawn by: Old Dominion Marine Railway Corp.; Commissioned by: Old Dominion Marine Railway Corp.
- - Permit Number: 40840, Address: 1038 W. 26th St., 1939, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 17, Folder 210)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.
- Equipment Storage Warehouse - Permit Number: 42016, Address: S/S 27th St., 1939, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1940-113 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  Drawn by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.
- Addition to Leigh Memorial Hospital - Permit Number: None, Address: 358 Mowbray Arch, 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1940-107 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects; Contractor: R. R. Richardson Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Leigh Memorial Hospital
- Elementary School Building for the City of Norfolk, Va. - Permit Number: None, Address: Newport Ave., 1947, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 18; Tag Number: None (Box 17, Folder 213)
  Drawn by: Vernon A. Moore, Architect, 305 Flatiron Bldg., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: City of Norfolk
- Proposed Garage and Office Addition for the Mary Jane Bakery - Permit Number: 49648, Address: 117 E. 16th St., 1944, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: None (Box 17, Folder 214)
  Drawn by: Thurmer Hoggard, Jr., McKevitt Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: G. F. Cox; Commissioned by: Mary Jane Bakery
- Addition to Mary Jane Bakery - Permit Number: None, Address: 1513 Monticello Ave., 1940, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1940-118 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect, Norfolk; Commissioned by: Mary Jane Bakery; Notes: Includes second drawing set for Addition to Mary Jane Bakery, 1513 Monticello Ave., 1/17/1944 (Permit # 50096), Bernard B. Spigel- Architect (2 sheets)
- Norfolk Linen Service - Permit Number: 41429, Address: 2419 Hampton Blvd., 1939, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1940-122 (Box 17, Folder 216)
  Drawn by: R. H. Edney, Designer; Commissioned by: Norfolk Linen Service
- National Youth Administration, Resident Center - Permit Number: None, Address: Newport Ave. and North Shore Rd., 1941, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 15; Tag Number: 1941-88 (Box 17, Folder 217)